http://www.proboat.com/privacy-policy

Last updated: (2017/10/20)
WoodenBoat Publications operates this website (https://www.proboat.com/). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site.
This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.
We will periodically send you email newsletters or promotional email about services offered by Professional BoatBuilder and its advertisers.  You can choose not to receive messages in the future by following the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each email. We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes without your permission.
Survey Emails. We may invite you to participate in user surveys asking for feedback on Professional BoatBuilder and existing or prospective products and services, as well as information to better understand our users. User surveys help us serve you better. Any information we obtain via surveys will not be shared with third parties, except in aggregate form.
Emails From You. If you send us an email, we will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.
Ads
Ads appearing on the ProBoat.com website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ProBoat.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
Digital Edition Access
Contact Information For general questions:
Editorial:
Subscription Information:
Advertising:
